what if woken
is offensive
how could that offend anyone as a
narcoleptic
i grew up in a very very religious
family and
so much so
that when halloween would come around as
a kid i was not allowed to dress up in a
secular costume no i had to be a
biblical character and never never one
of the good ones
because i was too sack religious i
always had to be so obscure and kind of
get the word out you know how
embarrassing that is to be seven when
you don't even know enough about your
own surrounding and you're
trick-or-treating with your friends and
you ring the doorbell and they're like
hey there's spiderman and there's batman
and they look at me and you're wearing
like a toga and like saying
i'm joseph of arimathea
yeah remember when they put the savior
in the tomb joseph is the guy who owned
the tomb
smaller character he had very important
in the new
but it was better for me to be out
trick-or-treating on the street than
back home i love my mother love her you
guys would love her hopefully you get to
meet her
i actually keep her ashes uh no i didn't
right by my bed uh she's not dead no
just smokes and uh
i figured if i had the ashtray no my mom
my mom would dress up
like the virgin mary and she wouldn't
give out snickers bars she'd give
communion
i really i hope i didn't offend anybody
you never know anymore what is offensive
and what isn't right that's that's and
it's generally the younger generation
that is the woke generation and i don't
know if there's a newsletter but i don't
know how you know there's probably a
word that's safe today a month from now
will somehow be on the no-fly list
i don't know what that word is but i do
know that i've had some younger folk
tell me oh you need to be woke you need
to what if woken
is offensive
how could that offend anyone as a
narcoleptic
we have suffered
some sleep and silence for far too long
i'm sick of you throwing the word walk
around
we're going to beat this we shall over
you just don't know what is offensive
anymore
i understand being nice and respecting
people
but i don't know
i met this gal not very long ago who had
just gotten out of a marriage
and trying to lend a shoulder to be to
lend some condolence i said i i
understand it could be very difficult to
be a divorcee oh you did not just call
me a divorcee
yeah i mean technically you're no longer
i mean oh my
that's so rude and demeaning you don't
call someone you just met a divorce say
what do you think before you open your
mouth divorce say
certified pre-owned
i don't know
is that better
slightly used price to sell low miles
new car smell little rear damage i don't
know
show me the carfax karen
it's just impossible to tell what
offends people
you